<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Impresa Insights</string>
    <string name="prompt_username">Username</string>
    <string name="prompt_password">Password</string>
    <string name="welcome">Welcome to</string>
    <string name="entreinfo">IMPRESA INSIGHTS</string>
    <string name="survey">Survey App</string>
    <string name="new_client">New Client</string>
    <string name="existing_client">Existing Client</string>
    <string name="correction">Correction</string>
    <string name="login_button">Login</string>
    <string name="title_activity_language">language</string>
    <string name="logout_title">Logout</string>
    <string name="logout_message">Are you sure yo want to logout?</string>
    <string name="yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="no">No</string>
    <string name="wrong_password">Wrong UserName or Password. Try again!!</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        "\nHello, my name is surveyor test, and Iwork with Innovations for Poverty Action(IPA) on a"
        "project to learn more about small business owners in your area. Through this project we "
        "hope to assist entrepreneurs in growing their businesses. We would like to ask you a few"
        "questions about you and your main business.\n\n"
        "Please note:\n\n"
        "1. Your participation is voluntary.\n\n"
        "2. There are no risks involved in completing this survey, either to you or your business.\n\n"
        "3. Your information will always remain confidential and well protected. No information "
        "will be shared with any third party, and no names will be published from the study.\n\n"
        "4. You should be as honest and accurate with your answers as possible as this information"
        "will be used to develop products and services that better meet the needs of small business"
        "owners like you.\n\n"
        "5. You can choose not to answer a question, or to stop the survey at any time.This will pose"
        " no risk to you or your business.\n\n"
        "6. This survey should take approximately 35 minutes of your time, depending on how you respond.\n\n"
        "By agreeing, you confirm that you understood the information above and have agreed to complete"
        " to complete the survey.\n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
</resources>
